Hello and welcome back to you and shorts and
as I have told in the last video,
all electric charges etc. should be paid, if you have
started then as soon as those
charges etc. are added, you will
see it in the name of Ola Care, there is an Ola Career
and an Ola Care Plus,
you will get the benefit of both of them, all these things are available in Ola Care,
₹2000 plus GST,
all these things are available in Ola Care Plus, ₹
3000 plus GST, this is the
difference between the two, you should see this, there are
so many differences in Ola Care and Ola Care Plus, these four things
are compulsory in both and the rest of these
things you will get in one, you will not get them in one,
Ola Care and Ola Care Plus
and along with this, it will start showing you here,
home service, pickup and drop,
Android Oxide Assistant, the prices of all three are being
shown to you on the right side,
all these plans have been started online